MARCUS MAYORGA

www.MarcusMayorga.com

RESUME OBJECTIVE

Web developer and multimedia artist with 5 years of experience developing graphics, video, and web-based content with a strong understanding of aesthetic and design principals. I am a fast learner and team player that can build professional websites from the ground up.

- Mayorga.ML@gmail.com
- 619 917 0961
- in LinkedIn.com/in/marcusmayorga

EXPERIENCE

WEB DEVELOPER

Freelance / June 2017 - Present

- Coordinates and communicates with customers to plan web development projects from concept through completion, utilizing a variety of web development tools and technology.
- Serves as webmaster for several projects promoting local business.
- Collaborates with clients to generate web content.

MULTIMEDIA ARTIST

5 Elements Martial Arts / June 2014 - Present

- Edits video footage for promotional purposes.
- Retouches and restores images based on the needs of project.
- Customizes CMS GUI for maximum compatibility across platforms and browsers.

VIDEO PRODUCTION SPECIALIST

Freelance / August 2013 - Present

Provides numerous freelance services for individuals and companies.
 The projects range from strictly camera work, editing only, and services that require both using different editing techniques per project needs.

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Freelance / August 2013 - Present

- Manages and coordinates graphic design projects from concept through completion.
- Collaborates with clients to create vision, conceive designs, and consistently meets deadlines and requirements.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML5 and CSS3

JavaScript

PHP

MySQL

React

AngularJs

WordPress

Git Version Control

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE MEDIA ARTS

Platt College, San Diego 2011 - 2013

FRONT END WEB DEVELOPER CERTIFICATION

San Diego Continuing Ed 2017 - 2018